You're about to learn powerful skills
for navigating complex relationships with
parents who struggle with abandonment
fears, emotional regulation, or grief.
This journey isn't about fixing your
parent or sacrificing your well being.
Instead, we'll explore how
to maintain connection while
establishing healthy boundaries.
You'll learn to understand the roots
of challenging behaviors, communicate
effectively during difficult moments,
Set compassionate boundaries and
practice essential self care.
By the end, you'll have practical
tools to create more balanced,
healthy interactions while honoring
both yourself and your parent.